{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D:  trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "B: giraffe", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: boy", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "D: helicopter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "C: stapler"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "D: helicopter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "D: Athens"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "B: calculator"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "B: giraffe", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B: square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "B: plumber"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "B: exciting", "gpt4o": "A: eraser", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "B: cream"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "D: write"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "B: France"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B: square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "B: anana", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "D: house", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "D: house"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "B: play"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "D: baseball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "C: black"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "D: loudspeaker"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "B: doctor"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D:  water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "B: milk"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "C: stapler"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B: square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "D: write"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "B: exciting", "gpt4o": "A: eraser", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "D: write"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "B: exciting", "gpt4o": "B: exciting", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "B: France"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "B: France"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: boy", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B: square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "D: waiter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "B: exciting", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "D: lettuce", "gpt4o": "B: anana", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "B: arm", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "B: exciting", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "D: lettuce", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "B: pink", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "B: pink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "B: plumber"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "C: tie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "B: plumber"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "D: house", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "B: odd"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "D: Athens"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": ": A: May"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "A: think", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "D: house", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "B: odd"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "D: helicopter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "D: helicopter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B:  swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "D: waiter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "D: lettuce", "gpt4o": "B: anana", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "A: cat", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "A: cat", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "B: odd", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "D: house"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "A: in", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "D: baseball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "B: anana", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "A: cat", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "D: Athens"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "C: aubergine"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "D: Athens"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "A: think", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "D: learn"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "B: exciting", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "B: exciting", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "C: Egyptian"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "D: lettuce", "gpt4o": "B: anana", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "D: house", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "D: house"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "A: cat", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "B: calculator"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "A: in", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "C: butcher's"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": ": B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "B: exciting", "gpt4o": "B: exciting", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B:  square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: boy", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "D: Athens"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "B: giraffe", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "B: plumber"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "A: eraser", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "D: loudspeaker"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "D: write"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "D: write"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "A: in", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "C: skyscraper", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "D: Athens"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "B: France"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "C: arm"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "D: waiter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "D: helicopter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B:  square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "A: mouse", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B: square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "B: lorry"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "D: write"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: anana", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": "B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "D: house", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "B: odd"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D:  trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "B: giraffe", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "A: eraser", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "C: cry", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " rabbit", " cow", " hen"], "answer": "table", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: rabbit", "gpt4o": "A: table", "commandr": "B: rabbit"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "A: bed", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["apple", " pear", " strawberry", " phone", " banana"], "answer": "phone", "deberta": "apple", "gpt3.5": "D: phone", "gpt4o": "D: phone", "commandr": "D: phone"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["helicopter", " square", " car", " tram"], "answer": "square", "deberta": "helicopter", "gpt3.5": "B: square", "gpt4o": "B: square", "commandr": "B: square"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pen", " pencil", " white", " eraser", " post-it", " clip"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "pen", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "C: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["doll", " snow", " rain", " wind"], "answer": "doll", "deberta": "doll", "gpt3.5": "A: doll", "gpt4o": "A: doll", "commandr": "B: snow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "D: waiter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["football", " tennis", " basketball", " water", " water polo", " baseball"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "football", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["actor", " doctor", " teacher", " three", " plumber", " proctor"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "actor", "gpt3.5": "D: three", "gpt4o": "D: three", "commandr": "D: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "D: waiter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["oil", " garlic", " skirt", " basil"], "answer": "skirt", "deberta": "oil", "gpt3.5": "C: skirt", "gpt4o": "C: skirt", "commandr": "C: skirt"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "A: mouse", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["jump", " clap", " pencil", " read", " run"], "answer": "pencil", "deberta": "jump", "gpt3.5": "C: pencil", "gpt4o": "C: pencil", "commandr": "C: pencil"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "B: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "A: mouse", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " three", " plane", " train", " boat", " car"], "answer": "three", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "B: three", "gpt4o": "B: three", "commandr": "B: three"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cloudy", " rainy", " sunny", " star"], "answer": "star", "deberta": "cloudy", "gpt3.5": "D: star", "gpt4o": "D: star", "commandr": "D: star"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "B: cream"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Monday", " spring", " summer", " winter", " fall"], "answer": "Monday", "deberta": "Monday", "gpt3.5": "A: Monday", "gpt4o": "A: Monday", "commandr": "B: spring"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["three", " twenty", " seventeen", " laptop", " zero"], "answer": "laptop", "deberta": "three", "gpt3.5": "D: laptop", "gpt4o": "D: laptop", "commandr": "D: laptop"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["appetizer", " plumber", " teacher", " waiter", " painter"], "answer": "appetizer", "deberta": "appetizer", "gpt3.5": "B: plumber", "gpt4o": "B: plumber", "commandr": "B: plumber"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "B: France"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["milk", " pink", " coffee", " tea", " beer"], "answer": "pink", "deberta": "milk", "gpt3.5": "A: milk", "gpt4o": "B: pink", "commandr": "D: tea"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Spain", " France", " German", " England", " Singapore"], "answer": "German", "deberta": "Spain", "gpt3.5": "E: Singapore", "gpt4o": "C: German", "commandr": "E: Singapore"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Italian", " Spanish", " Egyptian", " China", " Chinese"], "answer": "China", "deberta": "Italian", "gpt3.5": "A: Italian", "gpt4o": "C: Egyptian", "commandr": "D: China"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pencil", " eraser", " baby", " ruler", " notebook"], "answer": "baby", "deberta": "pencil", "gpt3.5": "C: baby", "gpt4o": "C: baby", "commandr": "C: baby"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Dublin", " France", " Tokyo", " Athens", " Paris", " San Francisco"], "answer": "France", "deberta": "Dublin", "gpt3.5": "B: France", "gpt4o": "F: San Francisco", "commandr": "B: France"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["think", " interesting", " cry", " learn", " do", " dream"], "answer": "interesting", "deberta": "think", "gpt3.5": "A: think", "gpt4o": "B: interesting", "commandr": "B: interesting"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mother", " cousin", " aunt", " cup", " uncle"], "answer": "cup", "deberta": "mother", "gpt3.5": "D: cup", "gpt4o": "D: cup", "commandr": "D: cup"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "A: cat", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "D: loudspeaker"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " uncle", " tie", " shirt"], "answer": "uncle", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: uncle", "gpt4o": "C: uncle", "commandr": "C: uncle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "B: sink"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cat", " giraffe", " dog", " hamster", " turtle"], "answer": "giraffe", "deberta": "cat", "gpt3.5": "B: giraffe", "gpt4o": "B: giraffe", "commandr": "B: giraffe"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["water", " tea", " coffe", " cookie", " beer"], "answer": "cookie", "deberta": "water", "gpt3.5": "A: water", "gpt4o": "D: cookie", "commandr": "D: cookie"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " circle", " on", " at", " by"], "answer": "circle", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: circle", "gpt4o": "B: circle", "commandr": "B: circle"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["square", " circle", " triangle", " trousers", " rectangle", " pentagon"], "answer": "trousers", "deberta": "square", "gpt3.5": "D: trousers", "gpt4o": "D: trousers", "commandr": "D: trousers"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Albania", " Asia", " Africa", " America"], "answer": "Albania", "deberta": "Albania", "gpt3.5": "B: Asia", "gpt4o": "A: Albania", "commandr": "B: Asia"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lamb", " sock", " duck", " horse", " rooster"], "answer": "sock", "deberta": "lamb", "gpt3.5": "B: sock", "gpt4o": "B: sock", "commandr": "B: sock"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "A: gin", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dress", " jeans", " blouse", " grey", " socks", " shirt"], "answer": "grey", "deberta": "dress", "gpt3.5": "D: grey", "gpt4o": "D: grey", "commandr": "D: grey"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: boy", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["under", " on", " behind", " notebook", " above"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "under", "gpt3.5": "D: notebook", "gpt4o": "D: notebook", "commandr": "D: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["listen", " study", " tell", " happy", " watch"], "answer": "happy", "deberta": "listen", "gpt3.5": "D: happy", "gpt4o": "D: happy", "commandr": "D: happy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["break", " play", " do", " write"], "answer": "do", "deberta": "break", "gpt3.5": "A: break", "gpt4o": "A: break", "commandr": "B: play"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "D: balcony"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["John", " Tom", " Mark", " Mary"], "answer": "Mary", "deberta": "John", "gpt3.5": "A: John", "gpt4o": "D: Mary", "commandr": "D: Mary"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["pens", " notebook", " pencils", " erasers", " papers"], "answer": "notebook", "deberta": "pens", "gpt3.5": "A: pens", "gpt4o": "B: notebook", "commandr": "B: notebook"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glue", " scissors", " black", " paper", " pen"], "answer": "black", "deberta": "glue", "gpt3.5": "B: scissors", "gpt4o": "C: black", "commandr": "B: scissors"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eyebrow", " nose", " arm", " eyelash"], "answer": "arm", "deberta": "eyebrow", "gpt3.5": "A: eyebrow", "gpt4o": "C: arm", "commandr": "D: eyelash"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["zebra", " bee", " fly", " butterfly", " ant", " dragonfly"], "answer": "zebra", "deberta": "zebra", "gpt3.5": "B: bee", "gpt4o": "A: zebra", "commandr": "D:  butterfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["ruler", " calculator", " stapler", " loudspeaker"], "answer": "loudspeaker", "deberta": "ruler", "gpt3.5": "A: ruler", "gpt4o": "D: loudspeaker", "commandr": "B: calculator"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: Zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " sink", " fridge", " oven", " stove"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "B: sink", "gpt4o": "C: fridge", "commandr": "C: fridge"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": ": C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["cathedral", " church", " glove", " abbey", " convent"], "answer": "glove", "deberta": "cathedral", "gpt3.5": "C: glove", "gpt4o": "C: glove", "commandr": "C: glove"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "D: house", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "B: odd"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " daisy", " lily", " computer", " tulip"], "answer": "computer", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "D: computer", "gpt4o": "D: computer", "commandr": "D: computer"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouse", " dragonfly", " ladybug", " ant", " beetle"], "answer": "mouse", "deberta": "mouse", "gpt3.5": "B: dragonfly", "gpt4o": "A: mouse", "commandr": "B: dragonfly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Michael Jordan", " machine learning", " basketball", " baseball", " black"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Michael Jordan", "gpt3.5": "B: machine learning", "gpt4o": "B: machine learning", "commandr": "B: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["worked", " studied", " live", " walked"], "answer": "live", "deberta": "worked", "gpt3.5": "C: live", "gpt4o": "C: live", "commandr": "C: live"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bread", " bakery", " butcher's", " market"], "answer": "bread", "deberta": "bread", "gpt3.5": "C: butcher's", "gpt4o": "B: bakery", "commandr": "B: bakery"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bath", " cottage", " skyscraper", " hut"], "answer": "bath", "deberta": "bath", "gpt3.5": "A: bath", "gpt4o": "C: skyscraper", "commandr": "C: skyscraper"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["gin", " cognac", " wine", " water"], "answer": "water", "deberta": "gin", "gpt3.5": "D: water", "gpt4o": "D: water", "commandr": "D: water"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["May", " twelve", " three", " eleven", " hundred"], "answer": "May", "deberta": "May", "gpt3.5": "A: May", "gpt4o": "E: hundred", "commandr": "B: twelve"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["skirt", " dress", " pen", " jacket"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "skirt", "gpt3.5": "C: pen", "gpt4o": "C: pen", "commandr": "C: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "A: glass", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rose", " cheese", " fruit", " vegetables", " fish"], "answer": "rose", "deberta": "rose", "gpt3.5": "B: cheese", "gpt4o": "B: cheese", "commandr": "B: cheese"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["rectangle", " circle", " book", " triangle", " heptagon", " tetrahedron"], "answer": "book", "deberta": "rectangle", "gpt3.5": "C: book", "gpt4o": "C: book", "commandr": "C: book"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bakery", " milk", " shoe shop", " post office", " kiosk", " restaurant"], "answer": "milk", "deberta": "bakery", "gpt3.5": "B: milk", "gpt4o": "B: milk", "commandr": "D: post office"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "C: carpet"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["box", " trombone", " tuba", " harp", " oboe", " triangle"], "answer": "box", "deberta": "box", "gpt3.5": "A: box", "gpt4o": "A: box", "commandr": "D: harp"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "B: cream"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": ": I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["I", " me", " him", " her", " them"], "answer": "I", "deberta": "I", "gpt3.5": "A: I", "gpt4o": "A: I", "commandr": "A: I"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eighty", " seven", " twenty", " fifty"], "answer": "seven", "deberta": "eighty", "gpt3.5": "B: seven", "gpt4o": "A: eighty", "commandr": "B: seven"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["museum", " hospital", " school", " balcony", " church"], "answer": "balcony", "deberta": "museum", "gpt3.5": "D: balcony", "gpt4o": "D: balcony", "commandr": "B: hospital"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["koala", " bear", " white", " zebra", " kangaroo", " horse"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "koala", "gpt3.5": "C: white", "gpt4o": "C: white", "commandr": "D: Zebra"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grapefruit", " anana", " raspberry", " lettuce", " grape", " avocado"], "answer": "lettuce", "deberta": "grapefruit", "gpt3.5": "B: banana", "gpt4o": "D: lettuce", "commandr": "D: lettuce"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "D: helicopter"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bedroom", " kitchen", " carpet", " dining room", " bathroom"], "answer": "carpet", "deberta": "bedroom", "gpt3.5": "C: carpet", "gpt4o": "C: carpet", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["dentist", " doctor", " postman", " hospital", " cashier"], "answer": "hospital", "deberta": "dentist", "gpt3.5": "A: dentist", "gpt4o": "C: postman", "commandr": "C: postman"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["table", " pen", " armchair", " wardrobe"], "answer": "pen", "deberta": "table", "gpt3.5": "B: pen", "gpt4o": "B: pen", "commandr": "B: pen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["shrimp", " whale", " tiger", " eel", " shark"], "answer": "tiger", "deberta": "shrimp", "gpt3.5": "B: whale", "gpt4o": "C: tiger", "commandr": "C: tiger"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["lift", " lorry", " pavement", " vacation", " crane"], "answer": "vacation", "deberta": "lift", "gpt3.5": "C: pavement", "gpt4o": "D: vacation", "commandr": "D: vacation"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["your", " book", " phone", " fan", " fame", " photo"], "answer": "your", "deberta": "your", "gpt3.5": "A: your", "gpt4o": "A: your", "commandr": "D: fan"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["muffin", " cupcake", " picture", " bun", " loaf", " croissant"], "answer": "picture", "deberta": "muffin", "gpt3.5": "C: picture", "gpt4o": "C: picture", "commandr": "C: picture"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["spoon", " cow", " fork", " knife", " napkin", " plate"], "answer": "cow", "deberta": "spoon", "gpt3.5": "B: cow", "gpt4o": "B: cow", "commandr": "B: cow"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["garlic", " lemon", " aubergine", " onion", " sweet potato"], "answer": "lemon", "deberta": "garlic", "gpt3.5": "A: garlic", "gpt4o": "C: aubergine", "commandr": "B: lemon"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["glass", " head", " arm", " leg", " hand", " foot"], "answer": "glass", "deberta": "glass", "gpt3.5": "B: head", "gpt4o": "A: glass", "commandr": "B: head"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["face", " swimming", " cycling", " climbing"], "answer": "face", "deberta": "face", "gpt3.5": "A: face", "gpt4o": "A: face", "commandr": "B: swimming"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bed", " dress", " tie", " skirt", " shoe"], "answer": "bed", "deberta": "bed", "gpt3.5": "A: bed", "gpt4o": "C: tie", "commandr": "B: dress"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["train", " cream", " airplane", " helicopter", " ship"], "answer": "cream", "deberta": "train", "gpt3.5": "B: cream", "gpt4o": "B: cream", "commandr": "B: cream"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Europe", " Greece", " Italy", " Germany", " Spain"], "answer": "Europe", "deberta": "Europe", "gpt3.5": "A: Europe", "gpt4o": "A: Europe", "commandr": "B: Greece"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " orange", " potato", " raspberry", " kiwi"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "C: potato", "gpt4o": "C: potato", "commandr": "C: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["in", " boy", " or", " under"], "answer": "boy", "deberta": "in", "gpt3.5": "B: boy", "gpt4o": "B: boy", "commandr": "B: boy"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["bus", " van", " car", " fly"], "answer": "fly", "deberta": "bus", "gpt3.5": "D: fly", "gpt4o": "D: fly", "commandr": "D: fly"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["nice", " odd", " strong", " house"], "answer": "house", "deberta": "nice", "gpt3.5": "B: odd", "gpt4o": "D: house", "commandr": "B: odd"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["Ames", " Iowa", " Des Moines", " Story County", " machine learning"], "answer": "machine learning", "deberta": "Ames", "gpt3.5": "E: machine learning", "gpt4o": "E: machine learning", "commandr": "E: machine learning"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["green", " kitchen", " bathroom", " dining room", " garage"], "answer": "green", "deberta": "green", "gpt3.5": "B: kitchen", "gpt4o": "A: green", "commandr": "B: kitchen"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["word", " ball", " teddy", " doll"], "answer": "word", "deberta": "word", "gpt3.5": "A: word", "gpt4o": "A: word", "commandr": "B: ball"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["boil", " type", " fry", " chop", " steam", " rinse"], "answer": "type", "deberta": "boil", "gpt3.5": "B: type", "gpt4o": "B: type", "commandr": "B: type"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["white", " black", " red", " apple"], "answer": "apple", "deberta": "white", "gpt3.5": "D: apple", "gpt4o": "D: apple", "commandr": "D: apple"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["mouth", " white", " arm", " head", " nail"], "answer": "white", "deberta": "mouth", "gpt3.5": "B: white", "gpt4o": "B: white", "commandr": "B: white"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["grape", " plum", " fig", " potato", " peach"], "answer": "potato", "deberta": "grape", "gpt3.5": "D: potato", "gpt4o": "D: potato", "commandr": "D: potato"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eye", " arm", " foot", " soap"], "answer": "soap", "deberta": "eye", "gpt3.5": "D: soap", "gpt4o": "D: soap", "commandr": "D: soap"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["June", " four", " seventy", " twelve", " thousand"], "answer": "June", "deberta": "June", "gpt3.5": "A: June", "gpt4o": "A: June", "commandr": ": B: four"}
{"question": "Pick the odd word out:", "choices": ["eraser", " exciting", " ugly", " fat", " beautiful", " slow"], "answer": "eraser", "deberta": "eraser", "gpt3.5": "A: eraser", "gpt4o": "A: eraser", "commandr": "B: exciting"}
